Okay then gang, in this lesson I want to talk about something called sub-agents which are really cool and they allow you to basically create a whole team working on your project where each sub-agent can have a different area of expertise that can be isolated and configured to work on certain tasks.For example, we could make a unit test agent whose expertise and function would be to really hone in on writing and running tests.Or we could make a sub-agent who specializes in security audits.
好的，各位，在這一課中，我想討論一個叫做子代理的東西，它非常酷，基本上允許你建立一整個團隊在你的專案上工作，每個子代理可以有不同的專業領域，可以被隔離並配置為處理特定的任務。例如，我們可以製作一個單元測試代理，專注於撰寫和執行測試；或者我們可以製作一個專門進行安全稽核的子代理。
We could make a UX reviewer who specializes in providing feedback for new components by viewing them in a browser, etc.Now each of these sub-agents all run independently from each other.They have their own system prompts, tools they're allowed to run, and their own context window.So they're a really good way of isolating certain workflows and tasks.And what's really cool is that Claude Code can delegate tasks to them when it needs to.So you can kind of think of Claude Code as being maybe a senior developer
我們可以製作一個 UX 審查員，專門透過在瀏覽器中查看新元件來提供回饋，等等。現在這些子代理都彼此獨立運作，它們有自己的系統提示詞、允許執行的工具，以及自己的上下文視窗。所以它們是隔離特定工作流程和任務的好方法。而且真正酷的是，Claude Code 可以在需要時將任務委派給它們。你可以把 Claude Code 想成是一個資深開發者，
working on tasks, who then instruct the sub-agents to carry out certain work.And one of the main benefits of working this way is that each sub-agent has a specialized expertise, which we can fine tune to excel in a particular area through detailed system prompts.Also, because each sub-agent has their own isolated context window, it keeps their context clean and focused, leading to, I think, better results a lot of the time.
在執行任務，然後指示子代理進行某些工作。以這種方式工作的主要好處之一是，每個子代理都有專業的專業知識，我們可以透過詳細的系統提示詞對其進行微調，使其在特定領域中表現出色。另外，因為每個子代理都有自己隔離的上下文視窗，這讓它們的上下文保持整潔和專注，我認為在很多時候這能帶來更好的結果。
And it also means the main thread stays cleaner and trimmer if we do this correctly, because we're delegating tasks to those sub-agents.So it reduces the context overload in your main session.So then in this lesson, we're going to make a sub-agent who can use the Playwright MCP server to preview and review the UI and UX of new components once they've been made.And the workflow is going to look something like this.We're gonna use the custom slash command to tell Claude Code to make a new UI component for us.
這也意味著，如果我們正確地這樣做，主執行緒會保持更整潔和簡潔，因為我們將任務委派給那些子代理，這減少了主作業階段中的上下文過載。所以在這一課中，我們要製作一個子代理，它可以使用 Playwright MCP 伺服器，在元件製作完成後，在瀏覽器中預覽和審查新元件的 UI 和 UX。工作流程看起來會是這樣：我們要使用自訂斜線指令告訴 Claude Code 為我們製作一個新的 UI 元件。
Inside that command, we're gonna add an instruction telling it to invoke the UX reviewer sub-agent to review its work after it's made code edits.That sub-agent's gonna use Playwright to open a browser and look at the component from a UX perspective.Then it's gonna provide feedback to the main thread on Claude Code, which will make edits to the component based on that feedback.If needed, it can ask the UX reviewer again to review the code or review the
在那個指令中，我們要新增一條指示，告訴它在進行程式碼編輯後，呼叫 UX 審查員子代理來審查它的工作。那個子代理要使用 Playwright 開啟瀏覽器，從 UX 的角度查看元件。然後它要向 Claude Code 的主執行緒提供回饋，Claude Code 將根據那個回饋對元件進行修改。如果需要的話，它可以再次請 UX 審查員審查程式碼或審查
component in a browser and provide more feedback until eventually everyone's happy and the component is finished.So let's give this a whirl.So then let's start by making a new sub-agent which we can do by coming into the Claude Code chat session and using a command which is forward slash agents.Now when we do that, we're going to see a list of agents you've already created.Now we've not created any, so we can make one by selecting this Create New Agent option.
在瀏覽器中的元件，並提供更多回饋，直到最終大家都滿意並且元件完成。讓我們來試試看。那麼讓我們從製作一個新的子代理開始，我們可以進入 Claude Code 聊天作業階段，然後使用 /agents 指令來做到這一點。當我們這樣做時，我們會看到你已經建立的代理清單，我們還沒有建立任何，所以我們可以選擇「建立新代理」選項來製作一個。
Once we've done that, we can choose a scope for this new agent, either project or personal.I'm going to select the project scope so that anyone working on this project can use the sub-agent.Then we're going to get two options.You can get Claude to generate one for you, or you can manually make one from scratch.Now, what I'd like to do is have Claude make one for me, then just change it where I see fit.So, let's select that first option, and then we're asked to describe what this agent should do and when it should be used.
完成後，我們可以為這個新代理選擇範圍，可以是專案或個人。我要選擇專案範圍，這樣在這個專案上工作的任何人都可以使用這個子代理。然後我們會獲得兩個選項：你可以讓 Claude 為你生成一個，或者你可以從頭開始手動製作一個。我想做的是讓 Claude 為我製作一個，然後在我認為合適的地方修改它。所以讓我們選擇第一個選項，然後我們被要求描述這個代理應該做什麼以及何時應該使用它。
And I'm just going to paste in a summary of this agent now, which says, Expert UI and UX engineer who reviews the UI and UX of React components in a browser using Playwright, takes screenshots, then offers feedback on how to improve the component in terms of visual design, user experience, and accessibility.So then I'm going to hit enter and Claude Code's going to go ahead and make this new agent for us.
我現在只是要貼入這個代理的摘要，它說：「專業的 UI 和 UX 工程師，使用 Playwright 在瀏覽器中審查 React 元件的 UI 和 UX，截圖，然後就如何在視覺設計、使用者體驗和無障礙功能方面改進元件提供回饋。」然後我要按 Enter，Claude Code 就會去為我們製作這個新代理。
Now, at some point, it's gonna ask you what tools you wanna provide your agent with, and the default option is to allow all tools, but I'm gonna unselect the edit tools because I don't want to give the agent the power to edit files.I only want it to review the components and offer feedback.It's also gonna ask you which AI mode you wanna use for the sub-agent, and I'm gonna select the Sonic 4 model.Then it's gonna ask you what color you want the subagent to use when it's providing updates in the terminal.
在某個時候，它會問你想要為你的代理提供哪些工具，預設選項是允許所有工具，但我要取消選擇編輯工具，因為我不想給代理編輯檔案的權限，我只想讓它審查元件並提供回饋。它也會問你想為子代理使用哪個 AI 模型，我要選擇 Sonnet 4 模型。然後它會問你想要子代理在終端機中提供更新時使用什麼顏色。
I'm gonna go for the purple color, you choose whatever you want.And then finally, it's gonna give you a summary of the agent it's making, which you can confirm by pressing enter.Okay, so we can see that now we have this project agent called UI-UX-Reviewer that uses the site model.Let's close this off and if we open up this file tree we should see inside the Claude folder and agents folder with this markdown file for the agent.
我要選紫色，你選你想要的顏色。最後，它會給你一個它要製作的代理的摘要，你可以按 Enter 確認。好的，我們可以看到現在我們有這個叫做 UI-UX-Reviewer 的專案代理，它使用 Sonnet 模型。讓我們關閉這個，如果我們開啟這個檔案樹，應該就能在 Claude 資料夾和 agents 資料夾中看到這個代理的 Markdown 檔案。
So we've got some front matter at the top which is the name of the agent, a description and then down here the tools that it's allowed to use.Now it's headed the Playwright one right here or a few of the Playwright tools rather because we specifically said in the summary we wanted to use Playwright.The model and the colour.Then a bit of a description down here.
所以我們在頂部有一些 Frontmatter，包含代理的名稱、描述，以及下面它允許使用的工具。它在這裡列出了 Playwright 那個，或者更確切地說是幾個 Playwright 工具，因為我們在摘要中特別說了我們想使用 Playwright。還有模型和顏色，然後下面是一些描述。
Then we've got the actual workflow, so the setup, the visual documentation, how to analyze, some testing methodology.We're not going to read all this, but essentially it's created this for us, and the job of this agent now is to review components using the Playwright MCP in a browser.And you can edit this, by the way, if you want to.It's basically like a gigantic prompt for the sub-agent, which gets used when the sub-agentgets invoked.
然後我們有實際的工作流程，包括設置、視覺文件說明、如何分析、一些測試方法。我們不打算把這些都讀完，但本質上它為我們建立了這個，而這個代理的工作現在是在瀏覽器中使用 Playwright MCP 審查元件。你可以編輯這個，如果你想的話，它基本上就像是子代理的一個巨大提示詞，在子代理被呼叫時使用。
So by all means go through this and just edit anything that you don't agree with or any additional information that you want to add.Just add it.Okay so now we've got this sub-agent created we can go back to the custom UI component command we created earlier in the course.And remember this command instructs Claude Code to make a new UI component based on certain criteria.And now at the end, I'm going to paste in one final instruction, which tells Claude to invoke the new sub-agent we just created and ask it for feedback.
所以請隨意瀏覽這個，編輯任何你不同意的地方，或者新增任何你想要新增的額外資訊。好的，現在我們有了這個子代理，我們可以回到我們在課程早些時候建立的自訂 UI 元件指令。記住，這個指令指示 Claude Code 根據某些標準製作新的 UI 元件。現在在最後，我要貼入最後一條指示，告訴 Claude 呼叫我們剛才建立的新子代理並要求它提供回饋。
Once it has that feedback, it should implement it by updating the component.And then finally, if it needs to, it can ask for another review and more feedback.So then now everything is set up and ready to go.So let's give this a shot.And remember, we need to exit out of Claude code first of all, because we just made a change to this command, and then we're going to start the session backup again.
一旦它獲得了那個回饋，它應該透過更新元件來實作它。最後，如果需要的話，它可以要求再次審查並獲得更多回饋。所以現在一切都設定好並準備就緒了，讓我們試試看。記住，我們首先需要退出 Claude Code，因為我們剛才對這個指令做了更改，然後我們要再次啟動作業階段。
All right then, so let's use the UI component tool, if I can spell it components, like so.And then the component name is going to be modal.And I'm going to say make a clean modern looking modal, which also has a semi transparent backdrop.
好的，讓我們使用 UI 元件工具，如果我能拼對 components 的話，就像這樣。然後元件名稱是 modal（彈窗），我要說：「製作一個乾淨現代感的彈窗，同時具有半透明的背景遮罩。」
All right, so press enter.
好的，按 Enter。
All right, and we can see already that it has a little to-do list that it's going to work on.And right at the bottom down here, it's going to say review the component with the UI-UX-reviewer agent.So that's the final step.Okay, so it wants to do something.Yep, we'll allow that, and I'm going to allow for the rest of the session.
好的，我們可以看到它已經有一個它要完成的待辦清單，在最底部，它說要使用 UI-UX-Reviewer 代理審查元件，這就是最後一步。好的，它想做某件事，是的，我們允許，並且我要允許整個作業階段。
Okay, so now you can see it's invoked this UI/UX reviewer and that reviewer wants to open up a browser.Now in order to do that it wants to start the dev server, so I'm going to let it do that.
好的，你現在可以看到它已呼叫了這個 UI/UX 審查員，那個審查員想開啟一個瀏覽器。為了做到這一點，它想啟動開發伺服器，所以我要讓它這樣做。
And now it wants to navigate to the preview page, which is where Claude Code added that component to when it created it, so let's allow it to do this.
現在它想瀏覽到預覽頁面，也就是 Claude Code 在建立元件時將其新增到的地方，所以讓我們允許它這樣做。
And now on my other screen, I can see it's opened up the browser, it's over here, you can see, alright.
現在在我的另一個螢幕上，我可以看到它開啟了瀏覽器，就在這裡，好的。
And it's asking me for permission to take a screenshot, yes, I'm gonna allow it to do that.
它要求我許可截圖，是的，我要允許它這樣做。
So something else you can do through Playwright is click elements on a page, and now it's asking for permission to do that, so we'll say yes.
另外，你可以透過 Playwright 做的一件事是點擊頁面上的元素，現在它請求許可這樣做，所以我們說是。
And this is taking a long time, by the way, because there's so many different variants that Claude co-created for this modal.There's about seven or eight different things it needs to do on the web page to test everything.
順帶一提，這花了很長時間，因為 Claude Code 為這個彈窗建立了很多不同的樣式變體，大約有七八件不同的事情它需要在網頁上進行測試。
All right, and now it wants to resize the browser width, so it's even testing for smaller device screens, which is really nice.So I'm going to allow it to do that.
好的，現在它想調整瀏覽器寬度，所以它甚至在測試更小裝置螢幕上的效果，這真的很不錯。我要允許它這樣做。
All right, so eventually it finished its review process.And you can see now it's made some additional edits and these are all the features it's implemented.So we've got the color variants, we've got the different sizes, we've made sure it's good for accessibility.We've got these different interactions so we can close via the cross button, escape key, or the backdrop click.
好的，最終它完成了審查過程。你現在可以看到它進行了一些額外的編輯，這些都是它實作的功能：顏色變體、不同的尺寸、確保無障礙性良好，以及不同的互動方式，可以透過關閉按鈕、Escape 鍵或點擊背景遮罩來關閉彈窗。
These are the files created for the modal and the test.And then it's updated the page, the preview page right here to have interactive demos.
這些是為彈窗和測試建立的檔案，然後它更新了預覽頁面，在這裡加入了互動示範。
So it says right here, the UI UX reviewer gave it a five out of five stars and marked it production ready.Well, that is really good.So it obviously did a good job of making these components.So now let's view these in a browser.All right, so I'm just on the preview page and I've scrolled all the way down to the modal components.So we've got buttons here to open the modals.So I could click on primary and yeah, that looks pretty good.So we can close it via cross or clicking over here.I'm gonna try the secondary one and then press escape.
它在這裡說，UI UX 審查員給了它五顆星滿分，並標記為生產就緒，這真的很好，所以它顯然在製作這些元件方面做得很好。現在讓我們在瀏覽器中查看這些。好的，我就在預覽頁面上，我一路捲到了彈窗元件的地方。這裡有按鈕可以開啟彈窗，我可以點擊 primary，是的，看起來很不錯。我們可以透過關閉按鈕或點擊這裡來關閉它。我要試試 secondary 那個然後按 Escape。
Yeah, that closes it.Confirm, all right.And then we'll click on cancel.And then finally, we'll click on the cross.So we've got these different variants, which is really nice, different sizes.So that's small, medium.I think that's a little bigger.Large, yeah, a little bit bigger again.All right, so these are the features it's implemented.So that's nice.It's kind of documented it for me as well.So these are actually using, I think, the card component because the card components are up here.
是的，那樣關閉了它。Confirm，好的，然後我們點擊 Cancel，最後我們點擊關閉按鈕。所以我們有這些不同的樣式變體，這真的很好，不同的尺寸：小的、中的，那個稍大一點，大的，是的，又稍微大了一點。好的，這些是它實作的功能，很不錯，它也為我整理了文件。所以這些實際上使用了卡片元件，我想，因為卡片元件在這裡上面。
So you know, like I said earlier on in the series, that Claude code does get a little bit giddy sometimes.It likes to use the work it's done elsewhere in the application.So I think this is just an example of that.It's reusing the card component to tell me about this modal component it just created.So kudos, that's very nice.Anyway, all looks pretty good.Maybe I would make some tweaks here and there, but I think it's done a good job of creating and also testing this component in the browser.
所以，就像我在系列早些時候說的，Claude Code 有時確實會有點過於興奮，它喜歡在應用程式的其他地方使用它已完成的工作。所以我認為這只是一個例子，它重複使用了卡片元件來告訴我關於它剛才建立的彈窗元件，非常好，做得很棒。無論如何，一切看起來都相當不錯，也許我會在這裡做一些調整，但我認為它在建立和在瀏覽器中測試這個元件方面做得很好。
And one more thing really quickly, just because we've made a subagent to automate the review process, it doesn't mean you shouldn't review the work yourself, both in the browser and in the code.This is something I think is really important and something I always do to stay in the loop because even though everything looks okay in the browser, it doesn't mean it's coded correctly and you might find something you don't like.
還有最後一件事，快速說一下，僅僅因為我們製作了一個子代理來自動化審查流程，並不意味著你不應該自己審查工作，無論是在瀏覽器還是在程式碼中。這是我認為非常重要的事情，也是我總是做的事情，以保持在迴圈中，因為即使在瀏覽器中一切看起來都沒問題，也不意味著它的程式碼是正確的，你可能會發現一些你不喜歡的東西。
Also, if you're not looking over the code that Claude produces, you're going to find yourself out of the loop very quickly and find it harder to navigate the codebase in the future when you do need to dig into theWeeds.
另外，如果你不查看 Claude 產生的程式碼，你會發現自己很快就會脫離迴圈，當你確實需要深入研究程式碼庫時，未來會更難導航。